Podell, Bertram L.; Papers apap270
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Bills and Resolutions, 1963-1967; Undated; 3; 1.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains material related to legislative bills. In addition to the bills, files contain news clippings and correspondence. The material in these files are from Bertram Podell's service in the New York State Assembly.
  - Assembly Bills Introduced By Podell, with Outcomes, ca. 1966 (Flat-file 3)
  - Committee on Local Finance, Bills Introduced, Assembly or Senate, 1963 (Flat-file 4)
  - Committee on Local Finance: Legislative Program Commission on Estates, 1963-1965 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 1-3)
  - Committee Reports, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 4)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 376, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 5)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 378, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to the Sale of Bonds not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 6)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 780, To Amend the Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 7)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 781, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Sale of Bonds not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 8)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 1417, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Issuance of Bonds by School Districts, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 9)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 1421, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Bond Resolutions of a Town Subject to Referendum, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 10)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 3967, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Material Used in Construction of Artificial Swimming Pools, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 11)
  - Favorable, Intro 778, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to the Sale of Bonds Not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 12)
  - Favorable, Intro 779, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 13)
  - Favorable, Intro 4040, To Repeal General Municipal Law, Providing for the Distribution of Copies of Codes to Employees of a Municipality, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 14)
  - Favorable, Intro 4277, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Improvements to Golf Courses, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 15)
  - Favorable, Intro 4370, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to City School Districts Requiring Approval of Certain Bond Resolutions, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 16)
  - Instructions: Local Finance Committee, 1965; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 17)
  - Intro 359, To Amend the Code of Criminal Procedure in Relation to the Admissibility of Confessions, 1963-1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 18)
  - Intro 360, To Amend the Judiciary law, in Relation to Appointments Made by Certain Judges and Justices, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 19)
  - Intro 362, To Amend the Voting Age From Twenty-one to Eighteen Years, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 20)
  - Intro 365, To Amend the Conduct of the Annual Sessions of the Legislature, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 21)
  - Intro 369, Creating a Temporary State Commission to Study Legislative Procedure, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 22)
  - Intro 505, To Amend Administrative Code of New York City in Relation, to Accidental Death Benefits for Members of the Police Department, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 23)
  - Intro 834, To Repeal a Section of Labor Law Relating to the Exclusion of Agricultural Labor From the Benefits Under Unemployment Insurance Law, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 24)
  - Intro 835, To Amend Aspects of Workers Compensation Law, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 25)
  - Intro 1322, To Amend the Conversation Law, in Relation to Private Rights in Waters and Harmless Alterations in Streams and Lakes, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 26)
  - Intro 1446, Creating a Temporary State Commission to Study the Problems of Commuters Transported by Railroads in New York State, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 27)
  - Intro 1447, To Amend Education Law in Cities with more than One-million People, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 28)
  - Intro 1448, To Amend Education Law, in Relation to Public Records, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 29)
  - Intro 1450, To Amend Education Law in Relation to Examination Boards in Cities with more than One-million People, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 30)
  - Intro 1451, To Amend General Business Law, For the Sale of Articles of Merchandise in Spray Containers, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 31)
  - Intro 1452, To Amend Insurance law for Filing a Claim Against the Motor Vehicle Accident Indemnification Corporation, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 32)
  - Intro 1831, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Public Dump or Dumping Grounds, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 33)
  - Intro 1832, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Lighting Highways and Bridges outside of Villages, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 34)
  - Intro 1833, To Amend General Municipal Law, in Relation to Payment of Municipal Employees Upon Separation from Service, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 35)
  - Intro 2106, To Amend Education Law, Local Finance Law and Public Authorities Law, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 36)
  - Intro 2257, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Traffic Control Signals and Standards, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 37)
  - Intro 2258, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Drainage Facilities, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 38)
  - Intro 2372, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to Special Duties of Directors of Credit Unions, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 39)
  - Intro 2373, To Amend Multiple Dwelling Law, in Relation to Doormen in Multiple Dwellings, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 40)
  - Intro 2374, To Amend Penal Law, in Relation to all types of Hypodermic Needles, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 41)
  - Intro 2375, To Amend Highway Law, in Relation to Taxes on Property for Highway Purposes, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 42)
  - Intro 2377, To Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to the maintenance of Sidewalks, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 43)
  - Intro 2377, To Amend General Business Law in Relation to Definitions, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 44)
  - Intro 2378, To Amend Judiciary Law, in Relation to Judges and Justices Serving on Other Various Public Committees and Organizations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 45)
  - Intro 2578, To Amend Insurance Law, in Relation to Fidelity and Surety Insurance, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 46)
  - Intro 2662, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation to Maternal and Infant Care, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 47)
  - Intro 2800, To Amend Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Tests to Determine Alcohol Content of Blood, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 48)
  - Intro 3351, To Amend Corporate Business Law, in Relation to Certificates of Incorporation, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 49)
  - Intro 3352, Proposing and Amendment to Limit the Amount of Amendments to the Constitution, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 50)
  - Intro 3355, To Amend Education Law, in Relation to the Number of Regents College Scholarships, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 51)
  - Intro 3684, To Amend Family Court Art, in Relation to Auxiliary Services to Aid Family Court Jurisdiction, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 52)
  - Intro 3685, Proposing Amendments, in Relation to Taxing Powers of Certain Cities, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 53)
  - Intro 4059, To Amend Corporate Business Law, in Relation to Certificates of Merger of Subsidiary Corporations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 54)
  - Intro 4060, To Amend County and Town Law, in Relation to Certification of Claims, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 55)
  - Intro 4061, To Amend Mental Hygiene Law, in Relation to Changing the Name for Institutes of Mental Retardation, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 56)
  - Intro 4245, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation for the Care and Treatment of Persons Over the Age of Twenty-One, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 57)
  - Intro 4293, To Amend Workers Compensation Law, in Relation to Liability and Property Damage Coverage, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 58)
  - Intro 4423, To Amend General Municipal Law in Relation to the Cost of Urban projects in Towns, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 59)
  - Intro 4498, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to the Amount a Bank can Lend an Individual, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 60)
  - Intro 4563, To Amend Decedent Estate law, in Relation to Powers of a Fiduciary, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 61)
  - Intro 4819, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation to State Aid for Aid Pollution Control, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 62)
  - Intro 5069, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to Lenders of Small Loans, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 63)
  - Intro 5070, To Amend Membership Corporation Law, in Relation to the Power of Corporations to Invert Trust Funds, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 64)
  - Intro 5071, To Amend Highway Law, in Relation to Control of Advertising Devices, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 65)
  - Intro 5072, To Amend Election Law, in Relation to the Appointment and Tenure of Employees of Education Boards, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 66)
  - Intro 5323, To Amend Cooperative Corporation Law, in Relation to Stock and Non-stock Cooperative Corporations, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 67)
  - Original Bills-Local Finance, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 68)
  - Proposal: Local Government Consolidation- A Means to Greater Economy and Efficiency in New York, 1967 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 69)
  - Resolution 25, Moratorium on Payments due During the New York City Bus and Transit Strike, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 70)
  - Resolution 81, Joint Legislative Committee on Living Costs, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 71)
  - Resolution 82, Metropolitan Opera Association, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 72)
  - Resolution 99, Federal Milk Subsidy Program, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 73)
  - Resolution 117, Assembly Committee on Local Finance, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 74)
  - Resolution 152, Police and Law Enforcement Agencies within New York State, Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 75)
  - Resolution 153, Separate and Distinct Water Districts within New York State, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 76)
  - Resolution 155, Hospital and medical Resources, 1966; Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 77)
  - Bill and Resolution File: Corporation Laws, Undated (Box 1 (3-Bills and Resolutions), Folder 78)